[{"id": 2679, "question": "Tokyo University laboratory has developed a robot that never loses at the game of Rock Paper Scissors. That is because its visual processing abilities and fingers work together faster than any human brain. A video of the undefeated robot has been watched by more than 3 million viewers on YouTube since going online at the end of June. Tokyo University engineering professor Masatoshi Ishikawa has a good-natured response to frustrated human losers who accuse him of essentially creating a robot that cheats. \"It is not cheating. Every one millisecond the image processor decides and recognizes the shape the human hand is going to make. And then the robot can make a winnable shape one millisecond later than a human being. Only one millisecond, but a human cannot see this difference because the hu...\n\nQ: Ishikawa's explanation suggests that the robot  _  .", "options": ["proves to be dishonest", "is lucky to win the game", "works slower sometimes", "responds faster than humans"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 909, "question": "Travel can be a lifesaver. But in today's economy with airlines adding new fees almost daily and ticket prices sharply on the rise, many have written off travel as too expensive. However, with a few saving tricks and a little research, there are still lots of great deals to be had on airline tickets and more. Early Bird Gets the Deal. Travel experts say that there are certain times of day when more deals are available. Airfares can change three times a day as airlines adjust their prices to fill up flights. Early morning is when the fares tend to be lowest.www.zxxk.com What Wouldn't a Business Traveler do? Flying when business travelers don't can save you big money. Most business travelers fly on Mondays and Fridays, so Tuesday and Wednesday are the best days. Airlines will usually lower t...\n\nQ: Many people have to cancel their travel plan because they   _  .", "options": ["have no saving tricks", "consider economic reasons", "seldom do research", "can't have great deals"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 1892, "question": "108 cities in China took part in World Car Free Day on Saturday to promote environmentally-friendly transport and ease increasingly grid-locked city streets.It's a highlight of a nationwide urban public transport week.People were urged to take public transport,ride bikes or walk. To help out,more than 200 new buses took to the streets.And the Beijing Subway laid on 10 more trains for rush hour. A Beijing resident said, \"Today is Car Free Day,and I do find the traffic much better and the bus can go much faster.\" Another resident said,\"I spent only half an hour to go to work.It took me twice as long before. And I can find seat on the bus today.\" But in some areas not signed up for traffic control,endless lines of cars can still be seen. Some people say they just can't do without their cars. ...\n\nQ: Car Free Day will bring the following benefits except_.", "options": ["saving quite a lot of energy", "environmental protection", "improving road traffic", "facing more serious traffic problems"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 2424, "question": "Millions of girls grow up with the hope of becoming a famous singer. Some even win local talent competitions as children, but only a few such early successes and dreams turn into reality. Jessica Andrews is one of the few whose dreams have come true. Andrews, first taste of success came at the age of 10. She won a talent competition in her home town of Huntingdon, Tennessee, singing I Will Always Love You, originally sung by Whitney Houston. Houston's version of the song appeared on The Bodyguard sound track, which happened to be the first album Andrews ever bought. Within two years, talk of Andrews had spread to Nashville and caught the attention of producer Byron Gallimore, whose credits include work with Tim McGraw, Faith Hill, and Jo Dee Messina. With Gallimore signed on to produce, An...\n\nQ: Which of the following may NOT be Andrews' album?", "options": ["Now.", "Heart Shaped World.", "The Prince of Egypt.", "Who IAm"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 2104, "question": "Believe it or not, there're always some people who like staying up too late. However, sleeping early can bring us many benefits. 1. Healthy heart. Staying up late in the night is a way to hurt your body with high blood pressure and cholesterol . These are the risks associated with the heart. 2. Reduce stress. A peaceful sleep in the night relieves physical and mental stress. It relaxes the body and mind. With insufficient sleep you're risking your health with heart attacks and other diseases. 3. Improve memory. Sleeping early lets your mind arrange the thoughts well. Waking up early with a fresh mind will regain all of it. 4. Protect you from diseases. By sleeping late in the night you're only stressing yourself, which will increase the blood pressure and cholesterol levels. So sleep early...\n\nQ: How many hours should a man sleep at least according to the text?", "options": ["9 hours.", "8 hours.", "7 hours.", "6 hours."], "answer": 2}, {"id": 1861, "question": "Polynesian Cultural Center The Polynesian Cultural Center (P.C.C.) offers the best value for your vacation dollar. There is so much to see and do for the entire family. They offer a unique and authentic view not only of the Hawaiian culture, but also offer a taste of their Polynesian cuisines . The Gateway Buffet Package A fun activity for all ages, experience the beauty of true Polynesia with The Polynesian Cultural Center's newest package. Experience the 7 Polynesian Islands as they share with you their culture through song and dance. Enjoy Prime Rib & Seafood Dinner at the Gateway Restaurant, finishing the evening with the Horizons Night Show. Adult Price: $68.00 Child Price: $51.00 The Twilight Package--Ambassador's Fine Dining This activity is an excellent choice for those who want a ...\n\nQ: Tourists can experience the Polynesian culture mainly through   _  .", "options": ["the local people's dresses", "luxury services and places of entertainment", "songs and dances", "cuisines"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 275, "question": "This year, some twenty-three hundred teenagers from all over the world will spend about ten months in their US homes. They will attend US schools, meet US teenagers, and form impressions of the real America. At the same time, about thirteen hundred American teenagers will go to other countries to learn new languages and gain a new understanding of the rest of the world. Here is a two-way students exchange in action. Fred, nineteen, spent last year in Germany with George's family. In turn, George's son Mike spent a year in Fred's home in America. Fred knew little German when he arrived, but after two months' study, the language began to come to him. School was completely different from what he had expected --- much harder. Students rose respectfully when a teacher entered the room. They too...\n\nQ: Fred and Mike agreed that   _  .", "options": ["American food tasted better than German food", "German schools were harder than American ones", "Americans and Germans were both friendly", "There were more cars in the streets in America"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 2391, "question": "Every child has written their names on the beach at some point. But whereas most people's \"handwriting\" is washed away, one super-rich Arab sheikh has ensure that his graffiti will last a little longer. Hamad Bin Hamdan Al Nahyan, 63, has scrawled his name in sand on an island he owns with letters so big that they be seen from space. The word \"HAMAD\" measures 1,000 meters high and is a staggering two miles long from the \"H\" to the \"D\" on the Al Futaisi Island. And rather than allow the writing to be washed away by the ocean, the letters actually form waterways that absorb the encroaching tide. The ruler's name is even visible on Google's map service. Hamad dreamed up the idea and had his workmen work hard for weeks to craft the enormous piece of sand graffiti. It is not known how much it c...\n\nQ: Which of the following in NOT true according to the passage?", "options": ["Hamad is a man who wants himself to be well-known from apace.", "Hamad is a super-rich person who always does something unusual.", "Hamad is a man who is always so mean in his family", "Hamad is a man who boasts his fortune is second to the Saudi king's"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 3157, "question": "The British policeman has several nicknames, but the most frequently used are\"copper\"and\"bobby\". The first name comes from the verb \"cop\" meaning \"to take\" or \"capture\", and thesecond comes from the first name of Sir Robert Peel, a 19th century politician, who was the founder of the police force. An early nickname for the policeman was \"peeler\", but this name had died out. Visitors to England seem,nearly always, to be very impressed by the English police. In fact, it has become a joke that the visitors to Britain, when asked for his views of the country, will always say,at some point or other, \"I think your policemen are wonderful.\" Well, the British bobby may not always be wonderful but he is usually a very friendly and helpful character. A music-hall song of some years ago was called, \"I...\n\nQ: Which of the following is NOT true?", "options": ["The British policeman has some nicknames.", "The British policeman is wonderful.", "Only the British policeman knows the time very well.", "The British policeman is ready to help people."], "answer": 2}, {"id": 2723, "question": "Google Works Miracles Google(www.Google.com) is a daily miracle to millions of people. If the Internet had only this very fast search engine, it would have justified its existence many times over. It is the most popular search engine on the web with a 54% market share, ahead of Yahoo! You type almost anything, however unclear, into the space provided and in a second it has come up with hundreds of references. If knowledge is power, then Google commands the gateway. Yahoo Becomes Giant Yahoo(www.yahoo.com) was the first wonder of the web, and in many respects, it still is. It started in January 1994 when two California graduate students, Jerry Yang and David Filo, started compiling a database of links, mainly for their personal use. But well before the end of the year, it had become recogni...\n\nQ: What goods did Amazon sell when it started its business?", "options": ["Power tools.", "Mp3 players.", "Different books.", "Videos and games."], "answer": 2}, {"id": 2001, "question": "A new report says the number of foreign students at colleges and universities in the United States increased by three percent last year. This has been the first obvious increase since 2001. American schools last fall had 583,000 foreign students. The record is 586,000. That was set in 2002 after many years of gains. But after that the numbers fell. The terrorist attacks on September 11th, 2001 led to more visa requirements. Now stronger efforts are being made to get more foreign students to study in the United States. China remained in second place in front of South Korea but behind India, whichsent almost 84,000 students last fall. The number of Japanese fell sharply by nine percent, although it remained in fourth place. There were three percent drops from Indonesia and Kenya, the only Af...\n\nQ: After 2002, the number of foreign students in the USA fell mainly because   _  .", "options": ["Americans were worried that foreign students might attack them", "few American universities welcomed students from abroad", "their own countries could offer them a better education", "it was harder for foreign students to get permission to study in the USA"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 962, "question": "Every fall, many Jewish people around the world celebrate the holiday of Sukkot . They build huts in their backyards, and if it is warm and dry outside, they live in those huts for seven days and nights. Living in a sukkah is meant to remind Jewish people that for 40 years their ancestors lived in huts in the desert. In modern times, it has also become a reminder that many people do not have a place to call home. In 2010, an American reporter named Hoshua Foer was building his own sukkah when he came up with an idea. He wondered what it would be like to have a competition for people around the world to use their imaginations to create modern sukkahs. It would be a design competition. But the sukkah would have to be built according to Jewish laws. These laws are found in an ancient book cal...\n\nQ: According to Joshua Foer,   _  .", "options": ["imaginations are very important to win the competition", "sukkahs can be built at any place and in any shape", "the winning sukkahs will be included in Talmud", "competitors should follow laws made by him"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 2879, "question": "On the way home from school, Jack always passes a park. His mother said it was dangerous to pass by the park at night, but it is the fastest way home. Today, after finishing soccer practice, Jack was walking toward the park as usual. Suddenly, Jack heard someone calling him, \"Excuse me!\" Jack turned around, and there was an old woman. \"Yes, ma'am.\" Jack answered politely. \"Don't pass by the park tonight.\" Her voice was weak and dry. \"Okay, ma'am,\" said Jack carelessly. The old woman held Jack's hand strongly, and said, \"I mean it!\" Jack felt the hairs on his neck stand up. As soon as the lady let go of his hand, he started to run. This time, he ran so fast that he didn't have time to think where he was going. When he stopped, he realized he was in the middle of the park. He remembered what...\n\nQ: What does the story mainly tell us?", "options": ["An old lady scared Jack for fun.", "A movie was being made in a park.", "Jack was frightened by something unexpected.", "Mother told Jack a frightening story."], "answer": 2}, {"id": 2277, "question": "It was 1961 and I was in the fifth grade. My marks in school were miserable and, the thing was, I didn't know enough to really care. My older bother and I lived with Mom in an ugly multi-family house in Detroit. We watched TV every night. The background noise of our lives was gunfire and horses' hoofs from \"Wagon Train\" or \"Cheyenne\", and laughter from\"I Love Lucy\", or\"Mister Ed\".After supper, we'd lie on Mom's bed and stare for hours at the TV screen. But one day Mom changed our world forever. She turned off the TV. Our mother had only been able to get through third grade. But, she was much brighter and smarter than we boys know at the time. She had noticed something in the suburban houses where she cleaned books. So she came home one day, switched off the TV, sat us down and explained th...\n\nQ: We can learn from the beginning of the passage that   _  .", "options": ["the author and his brother had done well in school", "the author had been very concerned about his school work", "the author had spent much time watching TV after school", "the author had realized how important schooling was"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 169, "question": "Directions: Read the following passage. The passage is followed by several questions or unfinished statements. For each of them there are four choices marked A,B,C and D. Choose the one that fits best according to the information given in the passage. It may be open to discussion which city is the most beautiful in the world. But in terms of \" the most livable\", Melbourne has ranked top in a survey done by the Economist Intelligence Unit (EIU) in August. In fact, four cities Down Under are among the top ten most livable cities. The climate in Australia is warm and mild, particularly in major coastal cities. As a result, people spend much time outdoors. They go to the beach, to the countryside, or play sports outdoors in fields. Take Melbourne for example. The city features many open green ...\n\nQ: With the example of the African swimmer, the author intends to show that Australians   _  .", "options": ["are very good at swimming", "understand the feelings of the underdog", "are courageous in face of hardship", "understand that having fun and playing a game does not have to mean winning"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 878, "question": "A new international study shows that six people die every minute from smoking. That is 3 million deaths around the world every year. If the present rate of smoking continues, the number of deaths each year from smoking could rise to 10 million by the year 2020. The study describes smoking is the biggest cause of deadly diseases among grown-ups in industrial countries. So far most of the smoking deaths have happened to men, especially in developing countries. A researcher at the World Health Organization says 70% of Chinese men smoke more than 15 cigarettes each day. In Latin America about 50% of the men are smokers. There also are a very large number of smokers in Russia and in Eastern Europe. And 25% of all smoking deaths worldwide are in those areas of the world. Scientists say smoking w...\n\nQ: According to the passage, if there are 100 Chinese men smokers in the room, as a result,the number of cigarettes they smoke is at least   _   each day.", "options": ["about 1, 500", "5, 000 or so", "under 750", "over 1, 050"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 3337, "question": "Mars is the planet most like Earth.Flying to Mars is a difficult task for humans. There is an experiment with the name \"Mars 500\" in Russia.Six volunteers take part in the experiment.They come from China, Russia, France and Italy.They won't go to outer space.They will stay in small modules on the ground for 520 days.It's just like a real journey In the modules, they will experience a lot: flying to Mars, flying back and working on Mars.During the long \"journey\", the volunteers can only eat space food.They can shower every 10 days.They can call their friends or families.Anyone of them can _ if he doesn't feel well.This experiment helps scientists know how well humans will be on a long journey to Mars. Wangyue, 26, from China, is the youngest of the volunteers.He is a teacher at the China As...\n\nQ: How often can the volunteers take a shower?", "options": ["three times a month", "three times a day", "ten days a month", "ten times a month"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 1457, "question": "When, after a year of being alone on his island, Robinson Crusoe sees a footprint in the sand, the reader of Robinson Crusoe trembles. Will Crusoe find another human being to end his loneliness? Is the footprint the sign of an enemy? Since 1719, when Daniel Defoe wrote Robinson Crusoe, thousands of people who enjoy English novels have thrilled to this great adventure story. But few know how the story came to be written. Robinson Crusoe was the first English novel. Its birth brought together the misadventures of a Scotch \"failure\" and the untapped imagination of an aging English scribbler. Near the end of the Seventeenth Century, the hot-tempered Alexander Selkirk was charged with bad conduct while in church. Rather than face this charge, he ran away to sea. Several years later, Selkirk fou...\n\nQ: Alexander Selkirk spent four years on a desert island because_.", "options": ["he sought adventure", "he was hot-tempered", "he was afraid to face charges", "his ship was wrecked"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 1386, "question": "Many years ago, when I was fresh out of school and working in Denver, I was driving to my parents' home in Missouri for Christmas. I stopped at a gas station about 50 miles from Oklahoma City, where I was planning to stop and visit a friend. While I was standing in line at the cash register , I said hello to an older couple who were also paying for gas. I took off, but had gone only a few miles when black smoke poured from the back of my car. I stopped and wondered what I should do. A car pulled up behind me. It was the couple I had spoken to at the gas station. They said they would take me to my friend's We chatted on the way into the city, and when I got out of the car, the husband gave me his business card. I wrote him and his wife a thank-you note for helping me. Soon afterward, I rece...\n\nQ: The author planned to stop at Oklahoma City  _  .", "options": ["to visit a friend", "to see his parents", "to pay at the cash register", "to have more gas for his car"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 3120, "question": "As part of an effort to improve treatments for life-threatening illnesses, a team of scientists have created rabbits that glow in the dark. The efforts have produced two rabbits out of a litter of eight that went from being a normal, soft white to glowing green in the dark. The rabbits were born at the University of Istanbul as part of the cooperation between scientists from universities in Turkey and Hawaii. The rabbits glow to show that a genetic operation technique can work efficiently. \"The green is not important at all--it's just a marker to show the experiment can be done successfully,\" said University of Hawaii associate professor, Stefan Moisyadi. To produce the glowing effect, researchers injected jellyfish DNA into a mother rabbit's embryos. Then those embryos were put into the m...\n\nQ: What do we know about the glowing rabbits?", "options": ["Their fur became green after the experiment.", "They were chosen from a special species of rabbits.", "The color1 that they glow isn't of interest to scientists.", "They live shorter lives than ordinary rabbits."], "answer": 2}, {"id": 12, "question": "Give it five minutes I used to be a hothead. Whenever anyone said anything, I'd think of a way to disagree. I'd push back hard if something didn't fit my world-view. It's like I had to be first with an opinion -- as if being first meant something. But what it really meant was that I wasn't thinking hard enough about the problem. The faster you react, the less you think. Not always, but often. This came to a head back in 2007. I was speaking at the Business Innovation Factory conference in Providence, RI. So was Richard Saul Wurman. After my talk Richard came up to introduce himself and compliment my talk. That was very generous of him. He certainly didn't have to do that. And what did I do? I pushed back at him about the talk he gave. While he was making his points on stage, I was taking a...\n\nQ: What is the core argument that the author put forward?", "options": ["Dismissing ideas is an effortless thing to do so you should always protect ideas carefully.", "The right idea always starts from a wrong idea and you need to protect it from being dismissed.", "One should be careful when it comes to judge a new idea.", "Every idea, whether powerful or fragile deserves five minutes"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 149, "question": "Growing up in Philadelphia, Lieberman started cooking with his stay-at-home dad when he was seven. His food-loving family had two kitchens, and he quickly learned what was the best way to bake his cakes. Lieberman improved his kitchen skills during a year abroad beforo college, learning from a cook in Italy and study local specialties in Gerrnany, Spain and France. At Yale,he was known for throwing dinner parties, single-handedly frying and baking while mixing drinks for dozens offriends. Just for fun, he and some friends decided to tape a show named Campus Cuisine about his cooking. Lieberman was a real college student showing his classmate how to do things like making drinks out of dining-hall fruit. That helped the show become very popular among the students. They would stop Lieberman a...\n\nQ: What can we learn about Lieberman from the text?", "options": ["He is clever but lonely.", "He is friendly and active.", "He enioys traveling around.", "He often changes his menus."], "answer": 1}, {"id": 2399, "question": "European Work Experience Program(E.W.E.P.)is an independent British organization which began in 1991 in the city of London.E.W.E.P.provides the opportunity for students from the 25 countries of the European Union and nationals from Norway,Iceland,Switzerland and Liechtenstein to live in England,to gain work experience,to practice their English and to get a better insight into the British social and eulturallife. To apply you must meet the following requirements: *Preferred age: 18 to 28 years old *Be able to work in the UK for a period of at least two months. *Must have a good knowledge of English. *Due to work permit restrictions,European Work Experience Program Ltd will only select you if you are a European Union Member or national from Norway,Iceland,Switzerland and Liechtenstein. Europ...\n\nQ: Which of the following is NOT the purpose of the program?", "options": ["To get a lot of work experience.", "To improve their English rapidly.", "To have better understanding of the British culture.", "To make more money in Britain."], "answer": 3}, {"id": 1814, "question": "A 13-year-old American boy on Saturday became the youngest climber to conquer Mount Everest, the world's highest mountain. Jordan Romero from Big Bear, California, climbed up the 8,850-meter summit from the Tibetan side. On the same day, a Nepali man, Apa Sherpa, broke his own world record of climbing Everest when he reached the summit for the twentieth time. Apa Shepa's team set off from Nepal's capital, Kathmandu, last month, heading for the base camp on the Chinese side of the mountain. \"The team has just called in and believe that they are standing on top of Mt. Everest,\" Romero's blog said. \"Their dreams have now come true. Everyone is happy.\" The climbing has put Romero one step closer to reaching his goal of climbing the highest mountains on all seven continents . \"It is just a goal...\n\nQ: What would be the best title for the passage?", "options": ["The great dream of picking rocks from top of Mt. Everest", "The number of successful Mt. Everest climbs.", "California teen becomes youngest to climb Mt. Everest.", "Mt. Everest climbing becomes more popular."], "answer": 2}, {"id": 1485, "question": "\"No man is an island\" is a well-known line from John Donne's Devotion. It was written more than three hundred years ago. Even now people still agree with him. No one can live a completely lonely life. Without other people, life will become empty and sad. We all need to have friends. For some of us, although making friends is not difficult, feeling shy, we may not want to make the first move. It is also difficult at times to keep the friends we already have. There are many books about friendship, but Dale Carnegie's How to Win Friends and Influence People, written in 1936, is the most famous. This \"how to\" book about getting along with other people became a best seller. It was later put into 28 languages. Dale Carnegie's advice seems to be simple, but can his advice help you? Do you need to...\n\nQ: Some of us find it not easy to make friends because   _  .", "options": ["we are afraid of making bad friends", "we are shy to take the first action", "we feel sure that we already have enough friends", "we feel worried that we won't be able to keep our friends"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 1792, "question": "Have you ever wanted to achieve a goal and ended up doing tons of research on how to achieve the goal? As you learn more and more, it feels like you know less and less because when you learn something new, you find that there is a lot to know about those things. Sometimes, people will get stuck in this needing to gather more and more information. There's nothing wrong with learning a lot, but when you let learning get in the way of doing, you will never get going. When you never get going, you still never start having the things you want. Too much learning can paralyze you in terms of taking action. A better way to go about achieving a goal is to gather some information and immediately start taking action on the information you have gathered. Many times you will feel unprepared, and that's...\n\nQ: The author thinks that learning   _  .", "options": ["stops us from doing things", "prevents us from achieving a goal", "should be combined with practice", "means gathering more and more information"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 2086, "question": "Hair has always been an important sign of beauty, especially true for women.Next to the face, hair is one of the main qualities people look for when they consider a woman's beauty.Whether long or short, curly or straight, hair often gets a lot of attention. Each hair grows independently of other hairs.Not all hairs experience the same period of growth at the same time.During the period of active growth, which is called Anagen, hair grows at a rate of about or one centimeter a month.About eighty five percent of hair follicles are going through this process at any given time.This period can last from two to six years. The Catagen period of hair growth comes next.It is then that hair growth begins to slow down.This period usually lasts two or three weeks.Finally, hair growth comes to a comple...\n\nQ: The Catagen period is a period that   _  .", "options": ["the hairs start to fall out", "the hairs grow at a fast rate", "hair growth stops completely", "hair growth begins to slow down"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 1112, "question": "Joke l: A man was sitting reading his papers when his wife hit him round the head with a frying pan. \"What was that for?\" the man asked. The wife replied, \"That was for the piece of paper with the name Jenny on it I found in your pocket.\" The man then said, \"When l was at the races last week Jenny was the name of the horse I bet on.\" The wife apologized and went on with the housework. Three days later the man was watching TV when his wife hit him on the head with an even bigger frying pan, knocking him unconscious. Upon regaining consciousness the man asked why she had hit again. Wife replied, \"Your horse phoned.\" Joke 2: \"Do you believe in life after death?\" the boss asked one of his employees. \"Yes, sir, \" the new employee replied. \"Well, then, that makes everything just fine, \" the boss...\n\nQ: The husband in Joke 4 means that   _  .", "options": ["he is thankful for his selfless and lovely wife", "he realizes he is unlucky to have married his wife", "it is fortunate to experience so many unforgettable things", "his wife deserves all his love because of her devotion"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 1874, "question": "When people talk about Golden Age in Leadville, Horace Austin Warner Tabor and his second wife, Elizabeth McCourt must be included. Their story is becoming one of the legends of the Old West. H.A.W.Tabor was a school teacher in Vermont. With his first wife and two children he left Vermont in 1855 to settle in Kansas. Perhaps he was attracted by rumors of fortunes to be made in Colorado mines. A few years later he moved west to the small Colorado mining camp known as California Gulch, which he later renamed Leadville when he became its leading citizen. \"Great deposits of lead are sure to be found here.\"he said. As it turned out, it was silver, not lead, that was to make Leadville's fortune and wealth. Tabor knew little about mining himself, so he opened a general store selling everything fr...\n\nQ: What maybe talked about in the following part of the story?", "options": ["Tabor's children.", "Tabor's second wife.", "Tabor's first wife.", "Miners in Leadville."], "answer": 1}, {"id": 2819, "question": "When someone meets a stranger with the same hobby, that person immediately becomes a friend. People enjoy the company of others who share a similar interest. Often they will form a club and travel great distances to attend meetings where they can talk about their hobbies. Other people have such unusual hobbies that no one else can share them. Sometimes they try to do something better, faster or longer than anyone else in order to have their names included in the Guinness Book of World Records. A lady in Massachusetts may have the world's easiest hobby; she let her hair grow. Diane Witt has not cut her hair for twelve years. It is now eight feet (2.44 meters) long, and she will soon set a new world record and her name will be placed in the Guinness Book. A thirty-year-old man in Pennsylvani...\n\nQ: Which of the following is true?", "options": ["Diane Witt's hair is now eight meters long.", "A thirty-year-old man in Pennsylvania played the piano for forty-five days and eleven hours.", "A musician in Connecticut played the violin for forty-three hours.", "Two young women from England stayed in the shower for two hundred hours."], "answer": 1}, {"id": 2481, "question": "We live in a dangerous world. The figures for crime go up year by year. If you were attacked in the street, would you be able to defend yourself? Not very well probably, especially if someone was pointing a gun at you. We all see a lot of violence of films, but recently some programs on television showed how people can defend themselves without guns. For example, in one film a woman was attacked from behind. She threw the man, who was heavier and stronger than she was, over her head. Then she held him tightly on the ground. How? She knew Judo. Jiu-jitsu, as judo is sometimes called, means \"muscle science\" in Japanese. The student of judo needs to learn a lot about the body, its bones and muscles. Judo uses a number of \"falls\", \"holds\" and \"throws\". Someone who does not know judo cannot def...\n\nQ: Which of the following statement is true about the woman in the passage?", "options": ["The woman held the man over her head.", "The woman was heavier than the man.", "The woman was able to defend herself.", "The woman attacked the man from behind."], "answer": 2}, {"id": 1001, "question": "Zoe Chambers was a successful PR(Public Relations) consultant and life was going well -- she had a great job, beautiful flat and a busy social life in London. Then one evening in June last year, she received a text message telling her she was out of work. \"The first two weeks were the most difficult to live through.\" she said. \"After everything I'd done for the company, they dismissed me by text! I was so angry and I just didn't feel like looking for another job. I hate everything about the city and my life.\" Then, Zoe received an invitation from an old school friend, Kathy, to come and stay. Kathy and her husband, Huw, had just bought a farm in north-west Wales. Zoe jumped at the chance to spend a weekend away from London, and now, ten months later she is still on the farm. \"The moment I ...\n\nQ: The most important reason why Zoe went to visit Kathy's farm is that  _  .", "options": ["Zoe lost her job as a PR consultant", "Kathy persuaded her to do so", "Zoe got tired of the city life", "Zoe loved Wales more than London"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 1373, "question": "Nowadays more and more people are talking about genetically modified foods ( GM foods). GM foods develop from genetically modified organisms , which have had specific changes introduced into their DNA by genetic engineering techniques. These techniques are much more precise where an organism is exposed to chemicals to create a nonspecific but stable change. For many people, the hightech production raises all kinds of environmental, ethical, health and safety problems. Particularly in countries with long farming traditions, the idea seems against nature. In fact, GM foods are already very much a part of our lives. They were first put on the market in 1996. A third of the corn and more than half the cotton grown in the U. S. last year was the product of biotechnology, according to the Depart...\n\nQ: The passage mainly talks about  _  .", "options": ["the world's food problem", "the development in biotech", "the genetically modified foods", "the way to solve food shortages"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 3479, "question": "Once upon a time, on an isolated island in the Java sea, lived short people who dominated(, ) the food chain. Standing no more than three and a half feet tall, these human ancestors hunted giant rats, lumbering lizards , and _ elephants. It sounds a bit like a fairy tale, but it's true. Unearthed relics on the island uncovered the remains of a race of tiny human ancestors. Homo floresiensis, as the newly discovered species has been named, apparently could date back to 13,000 years ago. This means they have a lot in common with modern humans. So how and why did these people get so small? Scientists suspect that it's due to the fact that this race lived on an isolated island with limited resources. Take the miniature elephants for example. When elephants first came to the island either by sw...\n\nQ: According to the passage, getting smaller can make people and animals   _", "options": ["run quickly", "live longer", "live weaker", "run slowly"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 1775, "question": "Dear Santa Claus, My name is Amy. I am 9 years old. I have a problem at school. Can you help me, Santa? Kids laugh at me because of the way I walk and run and talk. I have cerebral palsy. I just want one day when no one laughs at me or makes fun of me. Love, Amy At radio station WJLT in Fort Wayne, Indiana, letters poured in for the Christmas Wish Contest. When Amy's letter arrived at the radio station, manager Lee Tobin read it carefully. He thought it would be good for the people in Fort Wayne to hear about this special third grader and her unusual wish. Mr. Tobin called up the local newspaper. The next day, a picture of Amy and her letter to Santa made the front page of the \"News Sentinel\". The story spread quickly. All across the country, newspapers and radio and television stations re...\n\nQ: The postman was a regular at the Hagadorn house because   _   .", "options": ["he had to send letters to Amy daily", "he was quite curious about Amy", "he went to encourage Amy frequently", "he was moved by Amy's story"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 2028, "question": "Vancouver. B.C.--For six months. Ted Schredd and Deanna Kopel cycled around North America to show others a way to help the environment. \"Nobody wants to breathe dirty air--but for the air to change. People have to stop driving cars,\" says Ted, \"If more people start riding bikes, the air will be cleaner.\" Ted started his trip alone. He had $160 in his pocket and plans to cycle around North America. He left his hometown of Vancouver, and when he arrived in San Diego he got the chance to make some extra money for the rest of his 13, 000 km trip. A cyclist he met asked him to speak at an environment meeting in Texas. Within a few hours, Ted was on a plane to the meeting and a big surprise. When he met Deanna at the meeting, they talked for six hours straight. It was love at first sight. The ne...\n\nQ: In what way does the story have a happy ending for Ted and Deanna?", "options": ["They got married during their trip.", "They got together with their relatives.", "They became very famous in America.", "They wrote a book about their experience."], "answer": 0}, {"id": 32, "question": "What does it mean to say that we live in a world of persuasion? It means that we live among competing interests. Your roommate's need to study for an exam may take priority over pizza. Your instructor may have good reasons not to change your grade. In such a world, persuasion is the art of getting others to give fair and favorable consideration to our points of view. When we persuade, we want to influence how others believe and behave. We may not always _ -- other points of view may be more persuasive, depending on the listener, the situation, and the merit of the case. But when we practice the art of persuasion, we try to ensure that our position receives the attention it deserves. Some people, however, object to the very idea of persuasion. They may regard it as an unwelcome interruption...\n\nQ: The passage states that some people object to persuasion because they think it is   _  .", "options": ["a danger to society", "difficult to do well", "unwelcome behavior", "never successful"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 852, "question": "Most people think about donating blood. However, very few actually do it. Even the most consistent ones donate an average of just three to four times during their lifetime. Now the officials in Sweden are trying to change the trend with the help of modern-day technology. The encouragement to donate again begins shortly after the donor leaves the clinic when he/she receives a \"thank you\" text. Though that certainly helps them feel appreciated, what is even more pleasing is the text they receive each time their blood is used to help someone in need. Karolina Wiberg, manager of the Stockholm blood service, believes this small gesture not only results in repeat donors, but helps bring in new ones. _ that was started in Stockholm has received such positive feedback that it is now being rolled o...\n\nQ: Why is another text sent to blood donors after a \"thank you\" one?", "options": ["To ask them for authorization.", "To inform them their blood is used.", "To remind them to donate blood immediately.", "To tell them the levels of blood groups."], "answer": 1}, {"id": 917, "question": "Joe Temper should have known better. After all, he works for a large auto insurance company. It won't hurt to leave the key in the truck this once, he thought, as he filled his gas tank at a self-service gas station. But minutes later, as he was paying the money, he saw the truck being driven away. In 2010, 1.6 million motor vehicles were stolen in the United States --one every 20 seconds. If present trends continue, experts predict vehicle thefts could be over two million every year by the end of the decade. Vehicle theft is a common phenomenon, which has a direct effect on over four million people a year. The cost is astonishing. Many police officials blame professional thieves for the large number of the thefts. It is a major moneymaker for organized crime. Typically, stolen cars are ta...\n\nQ: It is obvious that the Michigan program  _  .", "options": ["has an effect on the whole USA", "involves the development of a new safety system", "involves the construction of larger prisons", "involves much work but proves to be quite effective"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 1413, "question": "Some children are natural-born bosses. They have a strong need to make decisions, manage their environment, and lead rather than follow. Stephen Jackson, a Year One student, \"operates under the theory of what's mine is mine and what's yours is mine,\" says his mother. \"The other day I bought two new Star Wars light sabers . Later, I saw Stephen with the two new ones while his brother was using the beat-up ones. \" \"Examine the extended family, and you'll probably find a bossy grandparent, aunt, uncle or cousin in every generation. It's an inheritable trait,\" says Russell Barkley, a professor at the Medical University of South Carolina. Other children who may not be particularly bossy can gradually gain dominance when they sense their parents are weak, hesitant, or in disagreement with each o...\n\nQ: The study on bossy behavior implies that parents  _  .", "options": ["should give more power to their children", "should be strict with their children", "should not be so anxious about their children", "should not set limits for their children"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 689, "question": "Woody Guthrie left California for New York in 1940. There he met Alan Lomax, an expert on America's traditional music. He collected and recorded traditional American folk music, which had few fans at that time. When he heard Woody sing, Lomax knew he had found a true singer of American folk music. Lomax recorded many of Woody's songs for the Library of Congress. Three years later, Woody published a book called Bound for Glory. It was about his early life and travels. From this book people came to learn how Woody had spent his unhappy youth. His mother, Nora Guthrie, died of Huntington's Disease in 1929 when he was only seventeen years old. There was no treatment for the disease. About twenty years later, the disease also began to attack the son. Woody's health got worse and worse, and fina...\n\nQ: According to the passage, Woody died at the age of   _  .", "options": ["38", "44", "55", "63"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 3453, "question": "It was a physical class. But it was nothing like previous ones -- the class was \"attended\" by over 60 million students across China, and the teacher was not even on the planet: she was 340 kilometers above the earth. \"Hello, everyone. I'm Wang Yaping. I'll host your lecture today.\" Smiling to the camera, Wang, China's second female astronaut, started her video class on June 20 on board the Tiangong-1 space station. To show how Newton's Laws work in space, Wang and her fellow astronauts used simple items like balls and spinning tops. The highlight of the lecture was when Wang _ using a metal ring, something that only happens in zero gravity, where the surface tension of water is much higher than it is on the earth. She then took it a step further by pouring more water onto the film and turn...\n\nQ: One of the experiments shows  _  .", "options": ["object motion under weight conditions", "laws of physics under weightless conditions", "laws of physics under weight conditions", "how Newton's Laws work on the earth"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 3078, "question": "One summer day as I was heading to the teaching building I heard someone call my name. I turned around and I saw Philip ,a counselor at our admissions office , standing with another young man, Philip introduced me to him, Stephen, and reminded me that Stephen would be taking one of my classes. Stephen looked at me. With a somewhat painful expression, he asked if my class was going to be hard and if he would be able to pass. I introduced all the things that he would be expected to learn. As we talked, I saw Stephen's eyes getting big with fear. I told him to do all of his assignments, and to hand them in on time. Rather than being overwhelmed by all of the work, I told him the most successful students made a master calendar of all the assignments so they could plan their workload. As the fa...\n\nQ: According to the passage, the author  _  .", "options": ["wouldn't have met Stephen without the introduction of Philip", "told Stephen how to deal with his study.", "helped Stephen to get an A in his class.", "didn't believe that Stephen could study in college"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 1569, "question": "Most people know that awkward feeling when you step into an elevator with other people and try not to make eye contact. But new research suggests it may be down to a subconscious power struggle being played out as you make your way up or down. A study found that people decide where they stand based on a micro social grading, established within seconds of entering the lift. Rebekah Rousi, a Ph.D. student in cognitive science, conducted an study of elevator behaviour in two of the tallest office buildings in Adelaide, Australia. As part of her research, she took a total of 30 lift rides in the two buildings, and discovered there was an established order to where people tended stand. In a blog, she writes that more senior men seemed to direct themselves towards the back of the elevator cabins...\n\nQ: According to Rebekah Rousi, senior men intend to stand   _   of the elevator cabins.", "options": ["in the front", "in the middle", "near the side mirrors", "at the back"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 696, "question": "An old man went to live with his son, daughter-in-law, and a four-year-old grandson. The family ate together at the dinner table. But the elderly grandfather's shaky hands and failing sight made eating rather difficult. Peas rolled onto the floor. When he took the glass, often milk spilled on the tablecloth. The son and daughter-in-law became unhappy with _ . So the husband and wife set a small table in the corner. There, grandfather ate alone while the rest of the family enjoyed dinner at the dinner table. Since grandfather had broken a dish or two, his food was served in a wooden bowl. Sometimes when the family glanced in grandfather's direction, he had a tear in his eyes as he ate alone. Still, the couple blamed him sharply when he dropped a fork or spilled food. The four-year-old son w...\n\nQ: What did the little boy react to his parents' behavior?", "options": ["He blamed his parents.", "He went to eat with his grandpa.", "He said nothing and did nothing.", "He made a wooden bowl for them."], "answer": 3}, {"id": 2534, "question": "As computers become more popular in China , Chinese people are increasingly relying on computer keyboards to input Chinese characters . But if they use the computer too much , they may end up forgetting the exact strokes of each Chinese character when writing on paper . Experts suggest people , especially students , write by hand more . Do you write by hand more or type more ? In Beijing , students start using a computer as early as primary school . And computer dependence is more widespread among university students . Almost all their assignments and essays are typed on a computer . All the students interviewed say they usually use a computer . It's faster and easier to correct if using a computer . And that's why computers are being applied more and more often to modern education . But w...\n\nQ: We can draw the conclusion from the passage that    _    .", "options": ["more and more students will give up writing on a computer", "writing by hand will give way to typing by computer one day", "more and more students will pay attention to handwriting", "the typing article better expresses one's emotion and quality"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 3141, "question": "From March 29 to April 19, a new version of Death of a Salesman was performedat tne Capital Theatre as the first in a series of foreign classics to mark the 60th anniversary of the Beijing People's Art Theatre.The last time this play was performed in Beijing was 29 years ago. Death of a Salesman was created in 1949 by Arthur Miller, who used it to reveal the weakness of the \"American Dream\" .The main character, Willy Loman, believes wholeheartedly in American capitalism, and desires to \"succeed\" but his own greed _ him in the end.Death of a Salesman's first performance was a huge hit on Broadway, where it shocked the American theatre world, and strengthened the 33-year-old Miller's status as a master of American theatre.The play won the Pulitzer Prize for Drama, New York Drama Critics' Cir...\n\nQ: What would be the best title for the passage?", "options": ["Death of a Salesman Returns to Beijing", "Arthur Miller--a master of American theatre", "Willy Loman--winner of the Pulitzer Prize for Drama", "Death of a Salesman--a milestone of 20th century theatre"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 2453, "question": "Norway tops the list of countries that offers the best social policies for people over 60. Afghanistan is rated the worst. The rankings appear in the new Global Age Watch Index. Help Age International published the index of 96 countries that are home to 790-million people 60 and older. Chief Executive Officer Toby Porter said, \"For too long, older people have been excluded from international and national development planning. We have a world which is ageing fast. And what the index does is to compare and rank countries from best to worst countries in the world to grow old,\" he said. The Global Age Watch Index rates countries in four categories. \"Health, income, what we call capability - ability to carry on contributing employment. And then the final one about enabling environment - what do...\n\nQ: The so-called BRICS nations do not include  _  .", "options": ["Russia", "China", "South Africa", "New Zealand"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 513, "question": "Job advertising on the web Register a new account Log in to an existing account Promote your casual work, graduate or internship ,opportunity with an advertisement on the Careers Centre database free of charge. Your advertisement will be viewable to all university of Sydney students and appear in 'Job Alert' - a daily email to subscribing students. You can also target alumni (up to five years after graduation) - advertise on our database and it will be visible at AlumniOnline. If you advertise through the Careers Centre you will need to agree to our advertising terms and conditions. Unpaid work We are unable to advertise unpaid internship work experience or volunteer positions unless: the position fulfills part of a University curriculum and has faculty approval, or it is a volunteer posit...\n\nQ: What kind of people is the passage intended for?", "options": ["people recruiting employers", "members in the Careers Centre", "job-hunters in university of Sydney", "undergraduates who need to improve the ability to study and work"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 2243, "question": "Drownings, bicycle injuries, falls, and pedestrian accidents are the most common causes of childhood injury or death. Here's what you need to know to avoid tragedy: * Drowning: Each year, thousands of children die from drowning, with two-thirds of accidents occurring in the summer. To protect kids, parents should install multiple layers of protective devices, with each layer offering another opportunity to avoid a tragedy. Fences, door alarms, pool covers are all somewhat effective individually, but their effectiveness is increased dramatically when used in combination with one another. * Falls: Falls from heights kill 140 children under the age of 15 each year in the United States, and seriously injure three million more, making falls the leading cause of non-deadly injury for this age gr...\n\nQ: What is the point of the article?", "options": ["To introduce factors that cause risks for children.", "To give tips on what to do to prevent accidents about children.", "To explain why summer is a risky time for kids.", "To describe what to do to prevent accidents at home."], "answer": 1}]